In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the U as in FEW diphthong.
我们将学习如何发音 FEW 中的 U 双元音。
Diphthongs are a combination of two sounds.
双元音是两个音的组合。
They have a starting position and an ending position.
它们有一个起始位置和一个结束位置。
The first sound is the Y consonant.
第一个音是 Y 辅音。
Diphthongs are normally made up of two vowel sounds,
双元音通常由两个元音音组成，
but in this case,
但在这种情况下，
the Y consonant is acting as a vowel.
Y 辅音充当元音。
For example, in the word music.
例如，在单词 music 中。
The Y sound goes with the OO vowel to make a diphthong,
Y 音与 OO 元音结合形成双元音，
rather than with the M consonant to make a consonant cluster.
而不是与 M 辅音结合形成辅音群。
Music.
Music。
To make the Y sound,
要发出 Y 音，
the jaw drops a little bit.
下巴稍微下垂。
The lips may be relaxed,
嘴唇可以放松，
or they may begin rounding for the ending position.
或者它们可能开始为结束位置做圆唇准备。
The tongue tip is down,
舌尖向下，
lightly touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
轻轻触碰下前牙的后面。
The mid-front part of the tongue lifts and touches the roof of the mouth about here.
舌头的中前部抬起并触碰口腔顶部大约在这里。
It pushes forward against the roof of the mouth before pulling away.
它在拉开之前向前推压口腔顶部。
As we move the tongue on the roof of the mouth,
当我们移动舌头在口腔顶部时，
we close the vocal cords to get this sound.
我们闭合声带以获得这个音。
Which we add to the sound, .
我们将其添加到音中，。
We release it the same time we release the tongue.
我们在释放舌头的同时释放它。
To transition into the next sound,
为了过渡到下一个音，
we release right into the position of the OO as in BOO vowel.
我们直接释放到 BOO 中的 OO 元音的位置。
The tongue tip doesn't need to move.
舌尖不需要移动。
It remains touching the back of the bottom front teeth.
它保持触碰下前牙的后面。
The back part of the tongue lifts towards the soft palate.
舌头的后部抬起朝向软腭。
The lips round.
嘴唇圆起。
Let's study a word with this sound,
让我们研究一个带有这个音的单词，
use.
use。
Jaw drops just a little bit as the tongue lifts and presses forward against the roof of the mouth.
下巴稍微下垂，当舌头抬起并向前推压口腔顶部。
The lips flare in preparation for the rounding at the end of the diphthong.
嘴唇张开，为双元音结尾的圆唇做准备。
Tongue releases,
舌头释放，
lifts in the back,
后部抬起，
and the lips round.
嘴唇圆起。
In a stressed syllable,
在重读音节中，
the U diphthong curves up, then down.
U 双元音曲线上升，然后下降。
Use,
Use，
U.
U。
In an unstressed syllable,
在非重读音节中，
it's lower and flatter in pitch,
音调更低更平，
as well as quieter and quicker.
而且更安静更快。
U, U.
U，U。
The diphthong is unstressed in the word interview,
在单词 interview 中，双元音是非重读的，
U.
U。
Let's take a look at the word interview.
让我们看看单词 interview。
A little bit of lip rounding in the first position of the diphthong,
在双元音的第一个位置，嘴唇稍微圆起，
but in the ending position,
但在结束位置，
the lip rounding is subtle.
嘴唇的圆起是微妙的。
Not like in a stressed U diphthong.
不像在重读的 U 双元音中。
Let's compare the ending position of the stressed U diphthong above with the unstressed U diphthong below.
让我们比较上面重读 U 双元音的结束位置与下面非重读 U 双元音的结束位置。
In the stressed version,
在重读版本中，
the lips round much more.
嘴唇圆起得更多。
Generally, the unstressed version of a vowel or diphthong is more relaxed and doesn't take the full mouth position.
通常，非重读版本的元音或双元音更放松，不需要完整的口腔位置。
In this case, less lip rounding.
在这种情况下，嘴唇圆起得更少。
This is because we don't take as much time for unstressed syllables.
这是因为我们不花太多时间在非重读音节上。
They're shorter, so we simplify the mouth movements.
它们更短，所以我们简化了口腔动作。
Use,
Use，
U.
U。
Unstressed, interview,
非重读，interview，
U.
U。
You,
You，
U.
U。
You,
You，
U.
U。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Music, U,
Music，U，
music.
music。
Continue,
Continue，
U,
U，
continue.
continue。
Review,
Review，
U,
U，
review.
review。
Unite,
Unite，
U.
U。
Unite.
Unite。
Union,
Union，
U,
U，
union.
union。
Future,
Future，
U,
U，
future.
future。